David Rockefeller papers, Photographic Collection, Personal, Professional and Travel FA1862
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Hudson Pines staff party at the Playhouse, 1989 July 9 (Box 24)
- Mountains or along southern vinyards #1, 1989 Februrary (Box 24)
- #2 Mr. Rockefeller, Oman, 1990 February (Box 24)
- Tokyo - JY Ranch - Seal Harbor - Spring Moon - Carriage Drives - Italy - Mexico - Venezuela - Poland - Cruise in Turkey, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Box 26, Box 27)
- Americas Society, Chairman trip to Venezuela; Puerto Ordaz, Venezuela #2, 1989 February (Box 25)
- Merida, Venezuela; La Romana, Dominican Republic #4, 1989 February (Box 25)
- Loose photographs (Box 25)
- Power Dam on the Orinoco; Merida, Venezuela #3, 1989 February (Box 25)
- Loose photographs (Box 25)
- Warsaw, Poland - CFR trip, 1989 March (Box 25)
- Chadds Ford, Pennsylvania, 1989 May 5-6 (Box 25)
- Budapest, Hungary, 1989 March (Box 25)
- Bodrum, Turkey #1, 1989 June 23-24 (Box 25)
- Greek ruins at Knidos #2 (Box 25)
- Turkey #3, 1989 June 26-27 (Box 25)
- Turkey #4, 1989 June 28-29 (Box 25)
- Turkey #5, 1989 June 29-30 (Box 26)
- Turkey #6, 1989 July 2-3 (Box 26)
- Turkey, 1989 June-July (Box 26)
- Burial of Margaret de Cuevas in family cemetery, 1989 June 18 (Box 26)
- Burial of Margaret de Cuevas - Pocantico - Rockefeller Cemetery, 1989 (Box 26)
- Seal Harbor, 1989 August (Box 26)
- Cruising to Canada, 1989 (Box 26)
- Peggy and Roberto Mignati wedding - Pocantico; Seal Harbor; New house under construction at Livingston, 1989 August (Box 26)
- Peggy and Roberto's wedding reception - Tarrytown, 1989 October 21 (Box 26)
- Mark Rockefeller at Ocean View Farm, Australia, 1989 October (Box 26)
- Seal Harbor, 1989 August (Box 26)
- Joseph Reeds - Thanksgiving lunch - Macao, China, 1989 November (Box 26)
- Staff Christmas party on Bartlett's Island, Maine, 1989 December 18 (Box 26)
- Christmas with children and grandchildren, 1989 December 25 (Box 26)
- Vestfold, Norway - Fishing, 1981 June 19-22 (Box 26)
- St. Barts with Cisneroses and Solomons, 1982 January 15-18 (Box 26)
- St. Barts, 1982 (Box 27)
- Photos of Dads with beard - Christmas 1981 (Box 27)
- Loose photographs (Box 27)
- Africa - Senegal, Ivory Coast airports, 1982 February (Box 27)
- Pocantico Hills, 1982 April 18 (Box 27)
- Muscat, Oman - Hewitts - CFR trip #2, 1990 February (Box 28)
- Arizona, New Mexico #1, 1990 March-April (Box 28)
- Arizona, New Mexico #2, 1990 April (Box 28)
- St Barts, 1990 April (Box 28)
- Columbier and Gustavia, St. Barts #3, 1990 March (Box 28)
- Muscat, Oman #3, 1990 February (Box 28)
- Outdoors camping, 1990 (Box 28)
- Peggy and David at the J.Y., 1990 (Box 28)
- On our 50th anniversary, Wyoming, 1990 (Box 28)
- Visit to the ranch, New Mexico, 1990 April (Box 28)
- Sedona, Arizona - Tish Hewitt's land near Raton N.E. New Mexico #3, 1990 April 07-12 (Box 28)
- The Virgin Islands #4, 1990 March (Box 28)
- Columbier, St Barts, 1990 March (Box 28)
- Trip to Mexico with John Avery #1, 1990 February-March (Box 28)
- Prague, 1991 February 18-20 (Box 28)
- Visit to Prague, 1991 February 18-20 (Box 28)
- Prague, 1991 February 18-20 (Box 28)
- Middle East - Caribbean - NF ME - JY Ranch - Prague - Vienna - Bolivia - Chile, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Box 29, Box 41)
- Vienna, 1991 February 21-24 (Box 29)
- Untitled #2, 1991 March 15-17 (Box 29)
- Bolivia #1, 1991 March 15-17 (Box 29)
- Loose photographs (Box 29)
- Birthday party, 1990 June (Box 29)
- Birthday party for DR, 1990 June (Box 29)
- Chile, outside of Santiago #3, 1991 March 20-29 (Box 29)
- Chile with Edwards on their island in the South of Chile #4, 1991 March 20-27 (Box 29)
- Glacier Bay, Alaska #1, 1991 June (Box 29)
- Glacier Bay and Elfin, Alaska #2, 1991 June (Box 29)
- Untitled (Box 29)
- Sweden, Czech Republic, 1992 February (Box 29)
- Visit to gardens and Lord Carrington, England, 1991 June (Box 41)
- Trip to Czechoslovakia, Prague #2, 1992 February (Box 41)
- Loose photographs (Box 41)
- Drive over the Atlas Mountains, Morocco #2, 1992 (Box 41)
- Alaska - Pocantico - Seal Harbor - Morocco - Chile - Death Valley, California, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Box 31)
- Morocco, 1992 (Box 30)
- Untitled (Box 30)
- Chile, 1992 (Box 30)
- Untitled (Box 30)
- Death Valley, CA, 1992 (Box 30)
- Untitled (Box 30)
- Italy, 1992 (Box 30)
- Untitled (Box 30)
- Venice, 1992 (Box 30)
- Italy, 1992 (Box 31)
- England, 1992 (Box 31)
- Italy, 1992 (Box 31)
- The Peggy Rockefeller Rose Garden, 1992 (Box 31)
- Rose garden - Regent's Park, England, 1992 (Box 31)
- Untitled, 1992 (Box 31)
- Puebla, Mexico, 1992 July (Box 31)
- San Juan Islands, Washington #1, 1992 September (Box 31)
- Cruise in the San Juan Islands, Washington #2, 1992 (Box 31)
- Puebla, Mexico, 1992 July (Box 31)
- Cruise in the San Juan Islands, Washington, 1992 September (Box 31)
- Loose photograph (Box 32)
- Cloud Forest - Monteverde, Costa Rica #1, 1993 March 15-22 (Box 32)
- El Pacifico Farm, Costa Rica; The Agora, The Acropolis - Athens Greece #1, 1993 March-April (Box 32)
- Loose photographs (Box 32)
- Mexico - Baja California #2, 1993 January 28 (Box 32)
- Mexico - Baja California #1 (Box 32)
- Untitled photographs and slides (Box 32)
- Mexico - Baja California #2, 1993 January 28-29 (Box 32)
- Lapa Rios, Osa Peninsula - Costa Rica #3, 1993 March 15-22 (Box 32)
- Lapa Rios, Osa Peninsula, Corcovado National Park - Costa Rica #2, 1993 March 15-22 (Box 32)
- Athens, Greece - Plaka, Acropolis, Agora, Island of Aegina #2, 1993 April (Box 32)
- Loose photograph (Box 32)
- Mr. Watanabe and Mr. Takagi of Mitsubishi Estate, Tokyo, 1993 (Box 32)
- Cruise on Spring Moon; Carriage drive at Pocantico, 1993 May 29-June 7 (Box 32)
- Loose photographs (Box 32)
- Alaska, 1993 (Box 32)
- Alaska, 1993 July (Box 33)
- Loose photographs (Box 33)
- Prince William Sound, Alaska, 1993 July (Box 33)
- 1 - Valdez shopping; Ferry, October; MSP (Box 33)
- MSP (Box 33)
- JY Ranch - Seal Harbor - Bob and Janey, Cruise with Kemany - Baja Cabin, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Box 35)
  File Plan
  GB 19, SB B 11
- Ho Chi Minh City - Cu Chi Tunnels, Vietnam (Box 34)
- Ho Chi Minh City - Cu Chi Tunnels, Vietnam duplicates, 1993 (Box 34)
- Aiken, South Carolina, 1994 (Box 34)
- Brazil; Hudson Pines; San Francisco, 1993 November-1994 February (Box 34)
- Buddhist Temple - Hanoi, Vietnam, 1993 (Box 34)
- South Korea, 1993 (Box 34)
- South Korea duplicates (Box 34)
- San Francisco, Baja California, 1994 February-March (Box 34)
- Baja California, 1994 (Box 34)
- Baja California with the Solomons, 1994 March (Box 35)
- Untitled (Box 35)
- Cayman Islands, 1994 January (Box 35)
- Photos from Tokyo, 1994 (Box 35)
- Office birthday party, 1994 June 13 (Box 35)
- Argentina, 1994 (Box 35)
- Untitled (Box 35)
- Seal Harbor, Hudson Pines, 1994 (Box 35)
- Chile, 1994 March (Box 35)
- Chile, Argentina, 1994 March (Box 35)
- Hudson Pines, Landing of the Harvest Moon, 1994 June (Box 35)
- Cruise with Davis K., 1994 May (Box 35)
- Graduation from Brown, 1994 May 30 (Box 35)
- Untitled (Box 35)
- Visit of the Emperor and Empress of Japan to Kykuit, 1994 June (Box 35)
- Visit of the Praemium Imperiale, 1994 June (Box 35)
- Paraguay, 1994 March (Box 35)
- Scotland, Maine Camping and Dinner, 1994 (Box 36, Box 37)
- Malloy, Scotland, 1994 August-September (Box 36)
- Photos taken by Lady Kate in Scotland, 1994 August 28-September 8 (Box 36)
- Kmaydan-Rhum, Scotland, 1994 August-September (Box 36)
- Scotland, 1994 August-September (Box 36)
- Tribute to William Hewitt, 1994 September (Box 36)
- John's birthday party on his yacht, 1994 September 21 (Box 36)
- Rick and Jennifer wedding photos, Alaska, 1995 August 3 (Box 36)
- Peggy's birthday party, 1995 September (Box 36)
- Rockefeller University photos, DR and JDR, Jr. busts, DR's birthday celebration, 1995 June (Box 36)
- Thailand, 1995 November (Box 36)
- Mexico #1, 1995 December-January 1996 (Box 36)
- Sailing with the Edwards in Chile #2, 1996 February (Box 36)
- Cruising with the Edwards in Chile #3, 1996 February (Box 36)
- With the Edwards, 1996 February (Box 36)
- Tepoztlan, Mexico #2, Snow at Hudson Pines, Sailing in Chile #1, 1996 January-February (Box 37)
- Seattle, 1996 March (Box 37)
- St. Petersburg #2, 1996 October (Box 37)
- Oaxaca, Mexico, 1997 December (Box 37)
- Atlanta, 1997 November (Box 37)
- India, 1998 January 17-27 (Box 37)
- Germany/Palm Springs, 1998 March-April (Box 37)
- Bilbao, Spain - Frank Gehry Museum, 1998 May 2 (Box 37)
- Loose photographs (Box 37)
- Sauall - Mallorca, Columbia University International Advisory Committee, 1998 May 2 (Box 37)
- India, 1998 January 17-27 (Box 37)
- Majorca Spain - Italy - NYC - Seal Harbor - China - Paraguay, 1998 (Box 38, Box 39)
- Majorca, Spain, 1998 June (Box 39)
- Italy #4, 1998 June (Box 39)
- China, 1998 October (Box 39)
- Paraguay, 1998 (Box 39)
- Trilateral 25th Anniversary, 1998 (Box 39)
- Tonga and New Zealand, 1999 March (Box 39)
- Puebla, Mexico, 1999 January (Box 39)
- Tonga - New Zealand, 1999 March (Box 39)
- Tonga and New Zealand, 1999 February (Box 39)
- Tonga A, 1999 March (Box 39)
- Tonga B, 1999 March (Box 39)
- Tonga B56, 1999 March (Box 39)
- Tonga A74, 1999 March (Box 39)
- New York City, 1999 April (Box 39)
- Argentina - Cruise to Tonga New Zealand - Hong Kong with Judy K - Barcelona - JY Ranch - Seal Harbor, 1999 (Box 40, Box 41)
- Birthday party given for DR, 1999 June 30 (Box 40)
- New York City 1, 1999 June (Box 40)
- Hong Kong (Box 40)
- Chairman's Council events, 1999 (Box 40)
- Colombier, St. Barts, 1999 (Box 40)
- Untitled (Box 40)
- Tom Laughlin (JM), NYC, 1999 (Box 40)
- Untitled, 1999 (Box 40)
- Cambodia, Laos, Thialand, Cuba, Mexico, 2001 (Box 40)
- Native villages, Cambodia, 2001 (Box 40)
- Cordoba, Argentina; Seal Harbor, 2001 (Box 40)
- La Paz, Argentina Americas Society Trip, 2001 (Box 40)
- Sailing in England, 2001 June (Box 40)
- Trip to England, 2001 (Box 40)
- Brazil, also Seal Harbor, 2002 January (Box 41)
- Brazil, 2002 January (Box 41)
- Alaska, 2002 May (Box 41)
- Miranda wedding, Hudson Pines, 2002 October 19 (Box 41)
- Stephen's passage to Juneau, Alaska, 2002 May (Box 41)
- Mexico, 2002 September (Box 41)
- The David Rockefellers (Box 42)
- Seal Harbor, 1947 Canuel, California, 1949, 1947-1949 (Box 43)
- Tarrytown and Maine Family Nelson - Ronald - George S., 1950 (Box 43)
- Tarrytown Eileen at 4 months Seal Harbor, 1952 (Box 43)
- Seal Harbor, Pocantico Children Riding, Sailing, Picnicking - Nelson, 1947-1951 (Box 43)
- Cuba Bank Trip to Visits Sugar, 1947 (Box 43)
- J.Y. Ranch Trip, 1948 (Box 43)
- Hudson River Tarrytown Winter and Spring, 1948-1951 (Box 43)
- Caracas, Venezuela Inauguration President Gallegos, 1948 (Box 43)
- Trip with Father to Blue Ridge and Great Smoky Mountains, 1950 (Box 43)
- J.Y. Ranch, Father, Dave K. George Gilder, 1950 (Box 43)
- Brazil Cattle Ranch Nelson and Frank Jamieson, 1948 (Box 43)
- Ecuador and Bolivia, 1950 (Box 43)
- Peru Cusco Macho Picchu, 1950 (Box 43)
- Hudson Pines, Peggy with Dave and Abby, 1951 (Box 43)
- Seal Harbor Children in Mother's Garden, 1953 (Box 43)
- Coronation of Elizabeth II, Bordeaux Vineyards, Chateaux Lascombes, 1953 (Box 43)
- Kuwait - Air view Parts and Oil Facilities, 1953 (Box 43)
- Seal Harbor; Brazil on a fazenda with Nelson, 1948 (Box 43)
- Saudi Arabia lunch with Sheikh Salmon, 1953 (Box 43)
- Seal Harbor, Cruises, Hudson Pines, England, 1953-1954 (Box 45)
- Spain #2, El Escorial, 1954 (Box 45)
- Spain #4, Bull Fight at the home of Pedro Gandarian, 1954 (Box 45)
- Spain #5, Granada, 1954 (Box 45)
- Spain, 1954 (Box 45)
- Portugal, 1954 (Box 45)
- Canyon of the Yellowstone, Air view of Crater Lake and Mt. Hood, 1955 (Box 45)
- Hudson Pines all the family, 1955 June 11 (Box 45)
- Yellowstone National Park; Children, 1955 (Box 45)
- Puerto Rico, 1955 (Box 45)
- Brazil and France, Trip with Dave, Abby, Nera, Brazil with Nelson, 1956 (Box 45)
- Venezuela - Nelson, Brazil, 1956 (Box 45)
- Puerto Rice, Carl Brurmuns, 1956 (Box 45)
- Brazil, Fazenda Bodoquene; Venezuela (and a few of Tarrytown), 1956 April (Box 45)
- Boats in Maine, Seal Harbor, 1956 (Box 45)
- Beech Hill - Walk with All The Children, 1957 (Box 45)
- J.Y. Ranch The Patterson and DR Families, 1957 (Box 45)
- St. Barts on the Wayfarer; W. Indies, 1958 (Box 44)
- Aerial Views of St. Barts before the house was built, 1959 (Box 46)
- Peru, Guano Island, 1958 (Box 44)
- Hudson Pines - Gardens - Horses; St. Barts - Wayfarer - Cruise, 1958 (Box 44)
- St. Barts with the Laurances on the Wayfarer, 1958 (Box 44)
- Newport, American Cup Races on the Wayfarer, 1958 (Box 44)
- Newport America Cup Races on the Wayfarer with the Aldriches, 1958 (Box 44)
- Peru, 1958 (Box 44)
- Belgium, Bruges - tour of the canals, Brussels - World's Fair, 1958 (Box 44)
- Kenya; Ethiopia, 1959 (Box 44)
- Africa - Belgian Congo, 1959 (Box 44)
- Kenya, Ghana, Nigeria, 1959 (Box 44)
- Brazil, Jaguar Hunt, Fazenda, 1958 (Box 44)
- Sudan, Ethiopia, 1959 (Box 44)
- South Africa, Kenga Park, 1959 (Box 44)
- South Africa, Game in Kenga Park, 1959 (Box 44)
- South Africa, Northern Rhodesia, Victoria Falls, Cape Town, South Africa, 1959 (Box 44)
- Canada, Salmon, Fishing in the Saguenay River, 1959 (Box 46)
- Greece with Niarhos, 1959 September (Box 46)
- Williamsburg, Canada, Mt. Katahdin, 1959 (Box 46)
- St. Barts, 1960 (Box 46)
- Seal Harbor, 1959 August (Box 46)
- Hudson Pines, Seal Harbor, 1959 (Box 46)
- Seal Harbor, Jack Tar I, Nelson, Tod, Peggy and David, 1950-1960 (Box 46)
- West Indies, 1960 (Box 46)
- Seal Harbor - Sailing, J.Y. Ranch, 1960 (Box 46)
- Canel Bay - Wayfarer, Tarrytown, 1960 (Box 46)
- Wyoming, 1960 July (Box 46)
- J.Y. Ranch, Wyoming, 1960 July (Box 46)
- St. Barts, Home at Colombier under Construction, 1960 (Box 46)
- 10 W. 54th, Pocantico, Seal Harbor, Washington, Egypt and Palestine, Prints, 1926-1929 (Box 48)
- Yellowstone Park, West, Redwoods in California, Prints, 1926 (Box 48)
- SS1 Tuxedo, Grandfather Ormond, Great Lakes, Niagara Falls, Prints, 1928 (Box 48)
- Florida, Prints, 1925-1929 (Box 48)
- Gettysburg/Washington, William's Guy, Prints, 1925-1926 (Box 48)
- Bicycle Trip to England, Scotland, and Wales, Prints, 1932 (Box 48)
- Bicycle Trip to England, Scotland, and Wales, Prints, 1932 (Box 48)